TADEU GABRIEL SANTOS VIEIRA

New Westminster - BC



778 835-5127



tadeugsvieira@gmail.com



| https://www.linkedin.com/in/tadeuvieira

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Three years professional experience in production planning and logistics. Despite of experience and education related to logistics and transportation field, available and desired for different field proposal. Results-oriented, highly-logical skills, continuous improvement drive, work well under pressure are my qualities.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Advanced user of Microsoft products and IT Concepts (Including Excel VBA)
- Study Abroad Participant Business English at Tamwood (Vancouver Canada; 2016)
- Six Sigma Green Belt Certified (RL & Associados; 2014)
- **Strong Cultural Awareness**
- Teamwork (Including multinational environment)
- **Decision Making**
- Committed
- Adaptability

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Brazilian Portuguese Native
- English General Training IELTS overall score 7.5 (Report form number: 21JP003578SANT512G)
- Japanese Beginner

EXPERIENCE

05/2022 - at moment CCL - Amazon DV1

Amazon Delivery Driver

Amazon Delivery driver Class 5 using Ford Transit Van 26m long, 10 hours shift.

Tadeu Gabriel Santos Vieira

Seiha English Academy - Japan

09/2020 to 02/2022

English teacher

Teaching English to Japanese kids 0-15 years old in a company with multinational employees, such as; Greeks, Americans, Canadians, Australians, Filipinos, Italians, Indians and Pakistanis. Brainstorming and activities in this multicultural environment were always interesting and exciting, sharing different perspectives and experiences.

Rumo Logística - Brazil

02/2017 to 01/2020

Production Planning and Operational Control Analyst

Management of assets, such as, locomotives, wagons and End-of-Trains for production planning in a railway company, controlling the loading and unloading of cargo. Rail traffic control decisions supporting client's demands and ensuring KPIs achievement, determining priorities that most provide high level service for clients.

Medium-term planning projects participant to support Rumo's expansion and operational improvement.

Oyama Gakuen - Brazil

03/2018 to 03/2019

Logistics Teacher

Logistics teacher to Japanese nationals working in Brazil learning Portuguese language.

VLI Logística

08/2014 to 07/2015

Intern

Rail incidents and accidents analysis at Centro - Leste railway VLI Corridor, monitoring level crossing safety issues, accidents statistics and management of KPIs.

Traffic and Transportation department of Itabira

08/2013 to 07/2014

Intern

Development of Itabira's Urban Mobility plan, general traffic issues analysis, and measurement of traffic marking paint to evaluate and calculate the payment to outsourcing companies.

EDUCATION

• **Degree:** Bachelor of Transportation Engineering.

Institution: Federal University of Itajubá.

Graduation: July/2016.

Certificates: Diesel engines and heavy equipment mechanics.

Institution: Senai – FIEMG. **Graduation:** July/2009.

Tadeu Gabriel Santos Vieira

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

• International driver license. (12 years of driving experience – Class 5)